(Sheldon:)Are you sure you have
enough comics?
(Sheldon:)You're going to be monitoring
the telescope for 12 hours,
(Sheldon:)and by my estimate,
you've only selected
(Sheldon:)seven hours of reading material.
(Sheldon:)That's even factoring in
(Sheldon:)your difficulty in parsing
American comic book idioms
like "Bamf!" and "Snikt!"
(Raj:)Is that racist?
(Raj:)It feels racist.
(Howard:)Don't be oversensitive.
He's calling you illiterate,
not your race.
(Raj:)Oh, okay. Good.
(Raj:)I don't need
more comics.
(Raj:)Howard's gonna stop by,
we're gonna play
(Raj:)Intergalactic Battleship
and Indian Monopoly.
(Sheldon:)I don't care for
novelty editions of Monopoly.
I prefer the classics:
regular and Klingon.
(Howard:)Actually, Indian Monopoly's
(Howard:)just like regular,
except the money's in rupees,
(Howard:)instead of hotels
you build call centers,
(Howard:)and when you pick a Chance card,
you might die of dysentery.
(Howard:)Just FYI,
(Howard:)that was racist.